## **ALEFIYA VAHANVATY**

Vancouver, BC 778-899-5087 alefiyavahanvaty@gmail.com

in linkedin.com/in/alefiyaV 🖸 alefiyaV.github.io

## Web Developer

	- 1	13		
ш	$  \cap  $	П	$\circ$	ı
		П	u	1

I am a design-minded and community-focused Web Developer with a flare for colour and composition. I'm always focused on the customer experience and commerciality in my contributions to an excellent product. I confidently prioritize tasks in dynamic projects and environments.

- Confidence in project presentation and public speaking.
- Obsessed with providing clean and clear wireframing, user stories, and, project planning steps.
- Quick prioritization of tasks, along with excellent time management skills ensures deadlines are met.
- Quantitative and qualitative research.
- I integrate easily into new teams and bring an open perspective

## Employment

Sales Planning Merchandiser

Oct 2018 - Feb 2018

IKEA Canada, Burlington Head Office

Employing IKEA standard rules, processes, and tools to sales merchandize the IKEA customer experience. Adjusting common practices to best suit the Quebec city market. Collaborated through the entire process in a small team comprised of a sales, visual, and, logistic counterparts.

Display Build Lead Jul 2017 - Oct 2018

IKEA Halifax

Lead, organized and coordinated the building of showroom furniture displays for the new IKEA Halifax store. Concurrently passing on company values to new recruits. Onboard until the 1 week after store opening.

Project Sales Lead Apr 2017 - Jul 2017

IKEA Coquitlam

Took the initiative to become a leading role during the entire project. Leading a group of sales coworkers and coordinating the day-to-day and big picture tasks to ensure the project went smoothly, within budget, and as inspirational to customers as possible while maintaining strong sales in Livingrooms.

Sales Coworker 2015 - 2018

IKEA Coquitlam

Showing a passion for sales by enthusiastically and actively selling IKEA products from all ranges to highly satisfied customers. Focus on range presentation, new product implementation and product research all with the customer and sales in mind.

Customer Success 2011 - 2015

IKEA Coquitlam

Handle and solve escalated customer complaints and complex customer situations. Using excellent communication skills and strategies to become a decision-maker in the department and exhibiting strong problem-solving skills to ensure a happy and satisfied customer.

Checkout Services 2010 - 2011

IKEA Coquitlam

Providing quick, efficient, and, accurate service to all customers in a fast-paced and hectic environment. Ensuring a positive customer experience as one of the last coworkers they see.

## Education

Web Development Diploma

Aug 2018 - Nov 2018

Lighthouse Labs

Immersive full-stack Web Development bootcamp. We covered languages, frameworks, and paradigms like JavaScript, Ruby, Rails, React, SQL, and more.

Certificate in Web Technologies

2015 - 2017

British Columbia Institute of Technology

Developed a foundation of Web skills with a focus on JavaScript, HTML, and, CSS. Learned design fundamentals and SEO

BA in Communication and Anthropology

2010 - 2013

Simon Fraser University

Focus on Race, Class, and, Gender relations with an emphasis on research and presentation.